Some decisions are life changing
Breaking & Exiting is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Peter Facinelli.
Harry, a charming house thief, gets more than he bargains for during an attempted burglary when he stumbles upon Daisy and
decides to save her from herself, sending both of them into a darkly comedic journey of self discovery and love.
Harry, played by Milo Gibson.
Daisy, played by Jordan Danger.
Chris, played by Adam Huber.
Hank, played by Joaquim de Almeida.
Lana, played by Justine Wachsberger.
Peter, played by James Kyson.
Breaking & Exiting is a 2018 American comedy-drama film written by Jordan Hinson,
directed by Peter Facinelli and starring Milo Gibson and Jordan Hinson.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and emotional.